Finding Aid for Philip F. Miller papers, 1932-1938 and 1954-1969.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Philip F. Miller papers 1932-1938 and 1954-1969
Miller, Philip F. (Philip Fall), 1915-1970.
6 linear feet
85502 Aa 2
Editor and publisher of the Daily Tribune; scrapbooks of newspaper columns and editorials, and miscellaneous.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Richard P. Miller (donor no. 5168 ) and came to the library in 1979.
The collection is open to research.
Philip F. Miller was editor and publisher of the Daily Tribune, a south Oakland County, Michigan, newspaper. He succeeded his father Floyd J. Miller in 1954 and continued until his death in 1970.
The collection consists of a miscellanea of correspondence, photographs, and biographical materials. There are also extensive files of his newspaper column "Personally Speaking" and the editorials he wrote for the newspaper.
Subjects:
American newspapers--Michigan--Grand Rapids.; American newspapers--Michigan--Royal Oak.; Grand Rapids (Mich.); Grand Rapids press.; Journalists--Michigan--Royal Oak.; Oakland County (Mich.); Royal Oak (Mich.); Royal Oak daily tribune.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Miller family.; Newspaper carriers.; Newspaper industry--Michigan--Oakland County.; Royal Oak (Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
- Miscellaneous
  - Biographical miscellanea (Box 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 1)
  - Printed material (Box 1)
  - Commemorative resolutions (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook of columns in The Daily Tribune and The Grand Rapids Press, 1932-1938 (Box 1)
  - Research papers re. The Daily Tribune (Box 1)
  - Photographs, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Newspaper column, "Personally Speaking"
  - 1954-1955 (Box 1)
  - 1956 (Box 1)
  - 1957 (Box 1)
  - 1958 (Box 2)
  - 1959 (Box 2)
  - 1960 (Box 2)
  - 1961 (Box 2)
  - 1962 (Box 2)
  - 1963 (Box 2)
  - 1964 (Box 3)
  - 1965 (Box 3)
  - 1966 (Box 3)
  - 1967 (Box 3)
  - 1968 (Box 4)
  - 1969 (Box 4)
  - 1970 (Box 4)
- Newspaper editorials
  - 1954-1955 (Box 5)
  - 1956 (Box 5)
  - 1957 (Box 5)
  - 1958 (Box 5)
  - 1959 (Box 5)
  - 1960 (Box 5)
  - 1961 (Box 5)
  - 1962 (Box 5)
  - 1963 (Box 5)
  - 1964 (Box 5)
  - 1965 (Box 6)
  - 1966 (Box 6)
  - 1967 (Box 6)
  - 1968 (Box 6)
  - 1969 (Box 6)
Related Material
The library also houses the papers of his father Floyd J. Miller and his son Richard P. Miller.